Khanh Nguyen

United States



khanhlinkedin@protonmail.com



linkedin.com/in/khanh-nguyen-021b491a9

Summary

My expertise area:

- Web development (both Front-end and Back-end)
- Blockchain development (Smart contract development and core development)

I'm very sensitive with new blockchain area like Defi, DEX and NFT. I've been involved in many Defi projects recently and built several staking pools

Experience



Site Reliability Engineer

CasperLabs

Jul 2020 - Mar 2021 (9 months)

Full Stack Engineer

Toptal

Aug 2019 - Aug 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Smart Contract Developer

Maple Finance

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020 (5 months)

https://www.maple.loans

Full Stack Engineer

Red Sand Group

Jul 2015 - Feb 2018 (2 years 8 months)

Frontend Developer

KIXEYE

Feb 2013 - Jun 2015 (2 years 5 months)

Education



🔼 Ho Chi Minh University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2009 - 2013

Skills

Rust (Programming Language) • React.js • Solidity • Front-end Development • javascript • Python (Programming Language) • Vue.js • Smart Contracts